{"data":[{"question":"What are you doing? \"I am waiting ___ my children. They should be back for dinner now.\"","a":"at","b":"after","c":"up","d":"for","answer":"4","explain":"\n- Wait for sbd\/sth","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"8","type":"1"},{"question":"It's freezing outside. You ___ put on your overcoat.","a":"had better","b":"had better to","c":"would better to","d":"would better","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Had better + infinitive without \"to\"","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"8","type":"1"},{"question":"Our parents ___ us stories when we were young.","a":"are used to telling","b":"were used to tell","c":"used to telling","d":"used to tell","answer":"4","explain":"\n- - Be\/get used to Verb_ing\/something: to have experienced something so that it no longer seems surprising, difficult, strange...\n- Used to Verb:\n+ Expresses the idea that something was an old habit that stopped in the past.\n+ Used to talk about past facts or generalizations which are no longer true","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"8","type":"1"},{"question":"Could you tell me what this phrase means? \"Sorry, I don't know it either. Let's look it ___ the dictionary.\"","a":"over in","b":"at","c":"for","d":"up in","answer":"4","explain":"\n- Look up: if you look up information in a book, on a computer etc, you try to find it there \n- Look for = search \n- Look at\/over: to turn your eyes towards something","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"8","type":"1"},{"question":"The teacher told the class to ___ their books and have a test.","a":"put by","b":"put away","c":"put up","d":"put on","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Put away:  to put something in the place where it is usually kept","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"8","type":"1"},{"question":"One of my classmates _________ the China Youth Corps for several years.","a":"has entered","b":"has been in","c":"has joined into","d":"has taken part in","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Subject: one of... is singular \n- Have\/has been in = join","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"8","type":"1"},{"question":"This laced hat ___ me.","a":"isn't fit","b":"doesn't fit for","c":"fits to","d":"doesn't fit","answer":"4","explain":"\n- Negative\/interrogative form of a normal verb: use auxiliary \"do\/does (interrogative); don't\/doesn't (negative) \n- Use \"does\" for singular subject","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"8","type":"1"},{"question":"Frank is the kind of person whom everybody likes to ___.","a":"make friends of","b":"make friends","c":"make friends with","d":"make friends to","answer":"3","explain":"\n- Make friends with somebody: to become friendly with someone","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"8","type":"1"},{"question":"We _________ you will write to us soon.","a":"need","b":"wish","c":"hope","d":"want","answer":"3","explain":"\n- Want\/need sbd to do sth\n-Wish, hope is grammarically correct in this sentence but \"hope\" is better in term of meaning","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"8","type":"1"},{"question":"As soon as he entered his home, Jason took ___ his coat and sat down.","a":"out","b":"off","c":"down","d":"away","answer":"2","explain":"- To take off: remove something, especially a piece of clothing","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"8","type":"1"}]}